[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 45, "question": "Your wife?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 46, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 56, "question": "When you hear those words, what do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 57, "answer": "I got a little emotional.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 65, "question": "How are you feeling now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 66, "answer": "I feel fine.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "RB", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 84, "question": "I mean how have your mom and dad been?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 85, "answer": "You know, I think my mom and dad took the news far worse than I did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 109, "question": "Your sisters?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 110, "answer": "They're -- you know, they're very supportive.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", ",", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 116, "question": "What kind of things?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 117, "answer": "I guess the most prominent symptom was my legs went numb for two months, something like that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "JJ", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "POS", "VBN", "TO", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VB", "PRP", "RP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 154, "question": "Do you still have moments, though, when you look in the mirror any morning you think why me, why now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NNS", ",", "IN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", ",", "WRB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 155, "answer": "Yes, it's usually at night when I'm injecting myself with a giant needle full of, you know, full of stuff that's supposed to, you know, keep me out a wheel chair.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "VBD", "``", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 162, "question": "What was the show?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 163, "answer": "I believe the title when I was involved was \"Stars on Stripes.\"", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", ":", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "JJ", ",", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 164, "question": "And you would have been doing what?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "VBG", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 165, "answer": "It was a -- kind of a military-style show, action/adventure, things like that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 169, "question": "And the only reason was because they couldn't insure you or what was the reason?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 170, "answer": "It was -- well, I was never told.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 186, "question": "Do you fear that others may follow suit?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 187, "answer": "To a degree.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 213, "question": "And what kind of life can Jack now expect, given he's 26 years old?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "MD", "VB", "RB", "VB", ",", "VBN", "PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 214, "answer": "Yes, Piers, thanks for having me.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jack"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "JJS", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 257, "question": "Endless people telling you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NNS", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 258, "answer": "You know, I think my biggest -- you know, from what I've been researching is, you know, stem cell research.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ":", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 263, "question": "Sanjay?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 264, "answer": "Yes -- yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 333, "question": "Benjamin Crump, what is your reaction to all the tape material that's come out today?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBP", "RP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 334, "answer": "Well, Piers, we're still trying to sort through it all.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Benjamin Crump"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 348, "question": "So in terms of that significance to how much we should believe in what George Zimmerman says in totality, how important is that, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "WRB", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "WP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 349, "answer": "Well, I think that's the crux of the matter, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Zimmerman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 385, "question": "Has that person come forward, made any statements?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", ",", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 386, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["last week"]}, "docId": "120621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 425, "question": "What is the purpose of putting this all out now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "DT", "RP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 426, "answer": "Well, the judge said last week that the information was going to come out.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 435, "question": "What would you say to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 436, "answer": "Well, the concern I have, Piers, is that I truly am not at liberty to do an analysis of the evidence.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "WRB", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "RP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 448, "question": "How much of a problem is it that his credibility is now being damaged?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 449, "answer": "As we've discussed, his credibility was certainly affected by the fact that he stood mute when his wife said something that turned out to be a misrepresentation to the court about the funds.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 456, "question": "The witness that George Zimmerman describes in the video today from the property directly adjoining where this incident finally took place, do you know if that witness has come forward and made a statement that corroborates what George is saying?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBG", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBD", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "CC", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 457, "answer": "That witness has made a statement.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Zimmerman", "George"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 465, "question": "How would you describe his mood?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 466, "answer": "Well, multifaceted.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 499, "question": "What was your reaction and your client's reaction to that bombshell, as it turned out to be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 500, "answer": "Piers, I was just going to use the same term you used.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 506, "question": "How do you feel the trial has gone in term of your client's interest and those of the other young people who came forward, who claimed they've been abused as children?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "NN", "CC", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "WP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "WP", "VBN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 507, "answer": "Well, I've been in the courtroom every day, from the opening statements until the end of the closing arguments and the jury charge.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jerry Sandusky"]}, "docId": "120621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "CC", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 519, "question": "Why are you so convinced, given the mountain of evidence to the contrary, that he is innocent of ever abusing a child?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", ",", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 520, "answer": "Well, the Jerry Sandusky that I knew and have come to know over the past 28 years spent his life trying to help kids overcome their circumstances.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "MD", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 524, "question": "I mean, would you ever have naked showers with boys of 12, 13, 14?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "VBN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "CD", ",", "CD", ",", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 525, "answer": "I certainly wouldn't now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 536, "question": "Do you feel that he's going to be acquitted?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 537, "answer": "I really have no idea.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "EX", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 545, "question": "Did you ever see anything that you thought was a little odd?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 546, "answer": "I don't think there's anything wrong with those behaviors.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Matt"]}, "docId": "120621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 558, "question": "Did you know Matt Sandusky, his adopted son?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP$", "VBN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 559, "answer": "Yeah, I knew Matt fairly well.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Matt Sandusky"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "DT", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "WP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 562, "question": "So are you as shocked as everybody else that he now is making it clear that he was abused by Jerry Sandusky, or claims to have been?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "VBG", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 563, "answer": "I'm not all that shocked by a kid who at the beginning of the trial is for him, at the end of the trial is against him.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jerry Sandusky"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120621pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 574, "question": "If Jerry Sandusky is as innocent as you think he is, why did this defense put up this strange claim that he suffered from this syndrome called Histrionic Personality Disorder?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "RP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 575, "answer": "Yes, I don't understand -- I don't claim to understand the rationale behind the attorney's actions.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Histrionic Personality Disorder"], "PERSON": ["Jerry Sandusky"]}}]